I'm here talking to you today about liners.
What they are?
What they are is a accent piece for your frame to ensure that you have a little classier look about it.
They come in different sizes, different shapes, different ways of looking at things some go in some go out, some just sit there.
Some have a little gold accent with them, some of them you have to go back to the fillet thought and put it in as well.
In my opinion your lighter should be as big as your frame.
If I was going to use this liner, I probably go to a different frame.
A little bit bigger frame the portion is quite nice then, you can use a little bitty liner in this.
The old school thought was if you had a piece of canvas you had to have a liner.
That is not the case today things have changed drastically it was just an old wise tail that was said down the way.